

# Navaneethan S Full Stack Developer

- Ocimbatore, India
- <u> 9750581966</u>
- ø srnavaneethan@gmail.com
- https://navaneethansr.github.io/

#### **Profiles**

in Navaneethan S

navaneethansr

**Skills** 

#### Web Technologies

Advanced

HTML5, JavaScript, PHP, Python, CSS3

# Web Frameworks

Intermediate

React.js, Angular

## **Tools**

Intermediate

Webpack, Git, Jenkins, JIRA, Docker

Certifications

# **AWS Certified Developer**

Amazon Web Services

2019

Languages

English

RWS

Tamil

RWS

#### Summary

Experienced Project Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Web Applications, Responsive Web Design, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), AngularJS, and Business Analysis. Strong program and project management professional with a Bachelor of Technology – BTech focused in Information Technology from Bannari Amman Institute of Technology.

#### Experience

#### **TheBay**

# November 2021 To March 2023

Senior Software Engineer

Bangalore, India

- Developing reusable components for the enterprise.
- Mentoring freshers and handling the scrum team.
- Being part of sprint planning and grooming sessions to enhance the user stories that helps in effective sprint planning.
- Lead the onshore Loyalty team and successfully implemented the MOP feature for holiday sale.
- Created Campaigns and Promotions for MOP go live project.
- Successfully completed SFCC SFRA PWA kit integration.
- Worked with SRE-OPS team to build CC/CI pipelines for internal repositories and production support.

## **MSys Technologies**

October 2018 To November 2021

Senior Software Engineer

Chennai, India

Web application which monitors and automates the Hyper-Converged storage. It is a one stop solution to create and maintain virtual machines, disks, storage pools etc., as a single unit.

- Interacted with the client to understand the requirements better and make the team clear and more precise with the quality deliverables.
- Developed reusable components, Handling the scrum team.
- Guided juniors in the team and trained them in the frameworks.

# Payoda Technologies

**July 2014 to August 2018** 

**Project Specialist** 

Coimbatore, India

- Translate UX wireframes into interactive features using AngularJs, HTML5, CSS and Less with cross browser compatibility.
- Developed reusable components.
- Adherence to coding standards and practices.
- Acted as Scrum master of the team.

#### Education

# Bannari Amman Institute of

August 2010 to May 2014

Bachelor's in Information Technology

Technology, Sathy

Coimbatore, India

7.5 CGPA

#### **Projects**

## **Interactive Dashboard**

Frontend Developer

Created an interactive analytics dashboard for a SaaS application, enhancing data visualization for clients.